highfive.com 2017-06-14

# Privacy Policy - Highfive

Last Updated: February 10, 2017

Thanks for using Highfive! This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use and handle your information and personally identifiable data when you access and use Highfive’s video conferencing and screen sharing system and all related software, applications and technologies available at and through the website [www.highfive.com](http://highfive.com/) (the “ **Site** ”) and mobile applications (such system, software, applications and the Site together, the “ **Service** ”).

To make it easier to read this Privacy Policy, we may refer to you, the user of the Service as well as anyone else you’ve given access to the Service, as “ **User** ”, “ **you** ,” “ **your** ,” and “ **yours** “. The terms “ **we** ,” “ **us** ,” and “ **our** ” refer to Highfive.

**What & Why**  
We are not in the business of collecting or keeping your information, but we do collect and use the following information and personally identifiable data in order to provide, improve and protect the Service:

_Our Service_. When you register to use the Service, we may collect, and associate with your account, information like your name, email address, phone number, payment info, and physical address (your “ **Personal Information** ”). If you give us access to your contacts, we’ll store those contacts on our servers for you to use. This will make it easy for you to do things like share send emails, and invite others to use the Service.  By using the Service and sharing your Personal Information, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We may use your Personal Information to contact you in the future to tell you about services we believe will be of interest to you. If we do so, each marketing communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to “opt out” of receiving future marketing communications. In addition, if at any time you wish not to receive any future marketing communications or you wish to have your name deleted from our mailing lists, please contact us as indicated below. If we ever intend to use any of your Personal Information in any manner that is not consistent with this Privacy Policy, we will inform you of our intended use prior to, or at the time at which, we collect the information.

_Usage and Other Personally Non-Identifiable_ _Data_. We collect certain personally non-identifiable information from and about the devices you use to access the Service. This includes things like IP addresses, the type of browser and device you use, the web page you visited before coming to our sites, and identifiers associated with your devices. Your devices (depending on their settings) may also transmit location information to the Service.  It is important to note that no personally identifiable data is available or used in this process and we cannot use this information to identify you.

_Cookies and Other Technologies_. We use technologies like cookies and pixel tags to provide, improve, protect and promote our Service. Cookies are small data files sent to your browser when you visit a site. We use cookies to do things like remembering your username preferences and settings for your next visit, keeping your account secure, understanding how you are interacting with our Service, and improving them based on that information. You can set your browser to not accept cookies, but this may limit your ability to use the Service. A pixel tag is a small piece of code that can be embedded on websites and emails. We use pixel tags to learn how you interact with our webpages and emails. This information helps us tailor and promote our Service.   If our systems receive a DNT:1 signal from your browser, we’ll stop using pixel tags to promote our Service on third-party sites accessed via that browser.

_Aggregated Data_.  In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve our users, we conduct research on user demographics, interests and behavior based on your Personal Information and other information provided to us. We compile and analyze this research on an aggregate basis, and may share this aggregate data with our partners. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

**With Whom**

We may share information, including your Personal Information, as discussed below, but we won’t sell it to advertisers or other third-parties.  If we ever intend to use any of your Personal Information in any manner that is not consistent with this Privacy Policy, we will tell you of our intended use prior to, or at the time at which, we collect such information.

_Others Working for Highfive_. Highfive uses certain trusted third parties to help us provide, improve, protect, and promote our Service (for example providing audio features and processing payments). These third parties will access your Personal Information only to perform tasks on our behalf and in compliance with this Privacy Policy.  These third party service providers may use cookies or pixals as well to collect information about your browsing activities over time and across different websites following your use of the Service. For example, we use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“ **Google** ”). Google Analytics uses cookies to help the website analyze how users use the Site and enhance your experience when you use the Service. For more information on how Google uses this data, go to [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).

_Other Users_. Our Service displays portions of your Personal Information like your name and email address to other users in places like your user profile and sharing notifications. Certain features let you make additional information available to other users.

_Administrators_. If your account has been assigned or provided to you by someone else, for example  your employer, an administrator or another user who has invited you to access and use the Service, they may have the ability to access and view your use of the Service and your Personal Information. Please refer to your employer’s internal policies if you have questions about this.

_Law & Order_. We may disclose your Personal Information to third parties if we determine that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) comply with the law; (b) protect any person from death or serious bodily injury; (c) prevent fraud or abuse of Highfive or any person; or (d) protect Highfive’s property rights.

**Security**

We take reasonable steps to protect the your Personal Information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, no Internet or email transmission is ever fully secure or error free. In particular, email sent to or from the Service may not be secure. Therefore, you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us via email. Please keep this in mind when disclosing your Personal Information to us via the Internet.

**Where**

_Around the world_. To provide you with the Service, we may store, process and transmit your Personal Information in the United States and locations around the world – including those outside your country.  By accessing and using the Service, you consent to Highfive storing, processing and transmitting your Personal Information outside of the country you reside, or are located, at the time you access and use the Service.  Your Personal Information may also be stored locally on the devices you use to access the Service. Highfive complies with the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Safe Harbor (“ **Safe Harbor** “) frameworks and principles. When transferring data from the European Union, the European Economic Area, and Switzerland, Highfive relies upon a variety of legal mechanisms, including contracts with our users. Highfive doesn’t rely upon Safe Harbor as a legal basis for data transfer but does adhere to the [Safe Harbor Privacy Principles](https://build.export.gov/main/safeharbor/eu/eg_main_018475) while specific guidance for the forthcoming EU-US Privacy Shield program is developed.

**Links to Other Web Sites**

This Privacy Policy applies only to the Service. The Service may contain links to other web sites not operated or controlled by Highfive (the “ **Third Party Sites** ”). The policies and procedures we described here do not apply to the Third Party Sites and the links from the Service to these Third Party Sites do not imply that we endorse or have reviewed the Third Party Sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy policies.

**Our Policy Toward Children**

Our Service is not intended for children. We do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not use the Service. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children never to provide personally identifiable information on the Service without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided personally identifiable information to us through the Service, please contact us, and we will make our best effort to delete that information from our databases.

**Changes**

If we are involved in a reorganization, merger, acquisition or sale of our assets, your Personal Information may be transferred as part of that deal. We will notify you (for example, via a message to the email address associated with your account) of any such deal and outline your choices in that event.

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time, and will post the most current version on our website. If a revision meaningfully reduces your rights, we will notify you.

**Contact**

Have questions or concerns about Highfive, our Service and privacy? Contact us at (legal@highfive.com) or at 500 Arguello St., Suite 200, Redwood City, CA 94063.
